RG 079:001, Department of Environmental Protection: Central Office
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Commissioner, 1957-2004
  - Stanley J. Pac, 1973-1987
    - Subject Files, 1977-1987; 1988-018
      - Governor’s Draft Responses, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
      - Hazardous Waste Siting Board (Box 15)
      - Household and other Non-Commercial Hazardous Waste (Box 15)
      - Health Dept. (Box 15)
      - Hearts and Flowers (Box 15)
      - Hydropower (Box 15)
      - Hurricanes (Box 15)
      - Hunting and Trapping (Box 15)
      - Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 15)
      - Hill Dye Co. (Box 15)
      - Hubbard Park (Box 15)
      - Housing (Box 15)
      - Housantonic Valley Association (Box 15)
      - Hazardous Waste Disposal Sites (Box 16)
      - Hazardous Waste-Incineration (Box 16)
      - Hazardous Materials Management Unit-Current and Previous Years (Box 16)
      - Hazardous Waste Management Task Force (Box 16)
      - Inland Wetland (Box 17)
      - Infrastructure Bridge Damage (Box 17)
      - Information and Education (Box 17)
      - I (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
      - Immigration Naturalization Service (Box 17)
      - Indian Affairs (Box 17)
      - Inland Wetlands (Box 17)
      - Killingly Pond (Box 17)
      - Interstate Transport and Pollutants (Box 38)
      - Interstate Conference on Water Problems (Box 38)
      - Inspector General Office (Box 38)
      - Insulation-UREA Formaldehyde (Box 38)
      - Integrated-Environmental Assistance (Box 38)
      - International Union of Operation Engineers (Box 38)
      - Invitations (Box 38)
      - Iroquois Gas Transmission System Pipeline (Box 38)
      - Island Brook Flood Control, Bridgeport (Box 38)
      - Alpha J (Box 38)
      - Johns River Ridge (Box 38)
      - Kemert Landfill (Box 38)
      - R (Miscellaneous) (Box 38)
      - K-F Brick Co. (Box 38)
      - Kerotene Co. (Box 38)
      - Killingly, Town of (Box 38)
      - Personnel Payroll (Box 38)
      - Interstate Highway (Box 18)
      - I-84 (Box 18)
      - USEPA (Box 18)
      - I-91/I-84 Interchange, Hartford Area (Box 18)
      - I-291 and I-291 Proposed Landfill (Box 18)
      - Nuclear-Current Year (Box 18)
      - Nuclear Publications/also Radiation (Box 18)
      - NPDES Program (Box 18)
      - Nuclear Power Plants (Box 18)
      - Natural Resources Center-Current and Previous Years (Box 18)
      - The Nature Conservancy, CT Chapter (Box 18)
      - Naugatuck, CT (Box 18)
      - Nautilus, USS (Box 18)
      - New Britain, City of (Box 18)
      - New Canaan, Town of (Box 18)
      - New England Governor’s Conference (Box 18)
      - New England Interstate Water Pollution Control Commission (Box 18)
      - New England River Basins Commission (NERBL) (Box 18)
      - New Haven/Stamford Dredging (Box 18)
      - New London (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous Interstate Sanitation/Comptrollers Files (Box 19)
      - Administrative files, L-Z (Box 20)
      - Law Enforcement (Box 42)
      - Laurel Park Landfill (Box 42)
      - LIQWACON (Box 42)
      - Life Be In It (Box 42)
      - Licensing and Revenues (Box 42)
      - Legislative Regulations Review Commission (LERC) (Box 42)
      - Legislative-Black and Hispanic (Box 42)
      - Legislature (State) (Box 42)
      - Legs hold Traps (Box 42)
      - Management Update News Letter (Box 42)
      - Managers Meeting, DEP (Box 42)
      - St. Managers Day (Box 42)
      - Management Incentive Plan (Box 42)
      - Management Advisory Council (Box 42)
      - Malls (Box 42)
      - M (Miscellaneous) (Box 42)
      - Long Island Sound Dredging (Box 42)
      - Long Island Sound (Box 42)
      - Local Assistance-Program Coordination (Box 42)
      - Lobsterman (Box 42)
      - Litter Control Unit (Box 42)
      - Land Acquisition (Box 44)
      - Land Use Education Council (Box 44)
      - Land Water Conservation Fund (Box 44)
      - Land Fill (Box 44)
      - AKA Currently Farriciella-Landfill Association (Box 44)
      - Labor Dept. (Miscellaneous) (Box 44)
      - Lake Waramaug (Box 44)
      - Lake Winter Green (Box 44)
      - Lake Management (Box 44)
      - Norwich Town Flooding (Box 44)
      - Norwalk River (Box 44)
      - Norwalk, CT (Box 44)
      - North Haven Mall (Box 44)
      - North Haven, Town of (Box 44)
      - Manchester, Town of (Box 21)
      - Mansfield, Town of (Box 21)
      - Maps and Publications (Box 21)
      - Marien Policy Reports (Box 21)
      - Mattabasett (Box 21)
      - Mediation Environmental Issues (Box 21)
      - Mental Retardation State Department (Box 21)
      - Meriden (Box 21)
      - Messerchmit Property (Box 21)
      - Mental Hydroxide Sludge Slides (Box 21)
      - Mid-Conn Project (Box 21)
      - Milford (Box 21)
      - Morningside Revetment (Box 21)
      - Mill River Hamden (Box 21)
      - Minimum Stream Flow (Box 21)
      - Model Airplane Flying (Box 21)
      - Monroe (Box 21)
      - Montville (Box 21)
      - Mohawk Mountain Ski (Box 21)
      - Motor Carrier Advisory Commission (Box 21)
      - MVD (Box 21)
      - Mumford Cove (Box 21)
      - Museums (Box 21)
      - Mute Swans (Box 21)
      - Mystic (Box 21)
      - Nuclear Publications (Box 23)
      - Nuclear Stations Emergency Operation (Box 23)
      - N (Miscellaneous) (Box 23)
      - National Association of Conservation Diet (Box 23)
      - National Governors Association (Box 23)
      - National Governors Environmental Subcommittee (Box 23)
      - National Outdoors Recreation Review Committee (Box 23)
      - New Milford Sewers (Box 24)
      - New York State, Department of Energy Conservation (Box 24)
      - Newington/New Britain (Central CT Expressway) (Box 24)
      - News Releases (Box 24)
      - Newspaper Clippings (Box 24)
      - Newtown, Town of (Box 24)
      - Noise Control Unit (Box 24)
      - New England Commissioners (Box 24)
      - CT Siting Council Report (Box 24)
      - New England Utilities Customer Assistance and Conservation Program (1980s-1990s) (Box 24)
      - Final New England Regional Environmental Impact Statement (Box 24)
      - Northeast Utilities-General (Box 24)
      - New Haven/North Haven (Box 24)
      - North Haven Mall, (Volumes 2-4), 1983 June (Box 24)
      - Personnel Purchasing (Box 25)
      - Personnel Resume (Box 25)
      - Personnel Staff Services (Box 25)
      - Personnel Department of Administration (Box 25)
      - Pesticides (Box 25)
      - Photographs (Box 25)
      - Planning and Coordination (Box 25)
      - Planning and Development (Box 25)
      - Quinnipiac Bridge (Box 26)
      - Radiation Control Unit-Current Year (Box 26)
      - Radon Gas (Box 26)
      - Railroad Advisory Task Force, Governor’s-Current Year (Box 26)
      - Recycling (Box 26)
      - Municipal Recycling Program (Box 26)
      - DEP Regulations (Box 26)
      - Plymouth, Town of (Box 27)
      - Polish National Alliance (Box 27)
      - Political (Box 27)
      - Portland, Town of (Box 27)
      - PFEC (Box 27)
      - Press Conferences (Box 27)
      - Press Releases (Box 27)
      - Private Sector Initiatives of Governors Council on Voluntary Action (Box 27)
      - Properties Review (Box 27)
      - Public Utilities Control Authority (Box 27)
      - Public Service Announcements (Box 27)
      - Public Works Division (Box 27)
      - Conference Purchasing Division (DAS) (Box 27)
      - Purchasing (DEP) (Box 27)
      - Oil-Includes Regulations and Offshore (Box 28)
      - Oil Spills (Box 28)
      - Old Lyme (Box 28)
      - Old Saybrook (Box 28)
      - O (Miscellaneous) (Box 28)
      - Office of Policy Management (OPM) (Box 28)
      - Open Burning (Box 28)
      - Open Space Task Force (Box 28)
      - Oxford-Larkin Bridle Trail (Box 28)
      - P (Miscellaneous) (Box 28)
      - Pachaug Forest Gallup Land (Box 28)
      - Pachaug Pond Boat Launch (Box 28)
      - Parking Spaces (Box 28)
      - Parks (Box 28)
      - Parks and Recreation Advisory Services (Box 28)
      - PCB (Box 28)
      - Relocation DEP (Box 29)
      - Remington Arms Gun Club (Box 29)
      - Reorganization DEP (Box 29)
      - Resources Recover-SWMU (Box 29)
      - Restaurant Menus (Box 29)
      - Revenue Services (Box 29)
      - Revenue Textile (Box 29)
      - Ride Sharing Program (Box 29)
      - River Front Recapture (Box 29)
      - Rocky Neck Parks and Recreation (Box 29)
      - Rooseter River Project (Box 29)
      - Route 7 (Box 29)
      - Roytyre (Box 29)
      - Roy Boe Bullehead (Box 29)
      - Boe, Roy LM Oral Arguments (Box 29)
      - Alpha’s (Box 29)
      - Salmon Restoration (Box 29)
      - Satan’s Kingdom (Box 29)
      - Savin Rock (Box 29)
      - Scantic River Flood Control (Box 29)
      - SCORP (Box 29)
      - Seismicity of US (Box 29)
      - Sewers (Box 29)
      - Seymour (Box 29)
      - Shelton (Box 29)
      - Sherwood Island (Box 29)
      - Silver Lake Dam (Box 29)
      - Silver Sands (Box 29)
      - Sleeping Giant Trail (Box 29)
      - State Implementation Plan (SIP) (Box 30)
      - State Implementation Plan/Revision Advisory Council (SIPAC) (Box 30)
      - State Police (Box 30)
      - Steel Brook Water Fund (Box 30)
      - DEP Steering Committee (Box 30)
      - Sterling, Town of (Box 30)
      - Stongington, Town of (Box 30)
      - Stratford, City of (Box 30)
      - Stratford Land Improvement (Box 30)
      - Structure of State Government (Box 30)
      - Suffield, Town of (Box 30)
      - Suggestion Program (Box 30)
      - Sulphur (Box 30)
      - Supper Fund (Box 30)
      - Soil Conservation Service (Box 31)
      - Soil Water Conservation District (Box 31)
      - Energy Recovery Facility (Box 31)
      - Solid Waste-Current Year (Box 31)
      - Windham, Town of (Box 31)
      - Solid Waste Management Advisory Council (Box 31)
      - Solvents Recovery (Box 31)
      - Somers, Town of (Box 31)
      - Regional Water Authority South Center, CT (Box 31)
      - South Windsor, Town of (Box 31)
      - Southington, Town of (Box 31)
      - Space Requirement Administration (Box 31)
      - Sprague, Town of (Box 31)
      - Springfield by Pass (Box 31)
      - Staff Meeting (Box 31)
      - Staff Service (Box 31)
      - Stan Chemical, Inc. (Box 31)
      - Stamford, City of (Box 31)
      - Visitors’ Register (Box 31)
      - Standardization Committee (Box 32)
      - State Association Training Program (Box 32)
      - State U.S. Dept. of Agriculture (Box 32)
      - State Emergency Responds Commission (Box 32)
      - State Ethics Commission (Box 32)
      - Sea State/EPA Agreement (Box 32)
      - Sip-State Implementation Plan, 1979 June 22 (Box 32)
      - SIP Appendix, 1979 June 22 (Box 32)
      - Superfund Amendments (Box 33)
      - Mute Swans (Box 33)
      - T (Miscellaneous) (Box 33)
      - TAGA van (Box 33)
      - Task Force on Accidental Toxic Chemical Releases (Box 33)
      - Task Force to Study Sale of Water Company Land (Box 33)
      - Thames River Outfall (Box 33)
      - Thomaston, Town of (Box 33)
      - Tidal Wetlands (Box 33)
      - Tire Disposal (Box 33)
      - Tolland, Town of (Box 33)
      - Torrington, City of (Box 33)
      - DEP’s Toxic Laboratory (Box 33)
      - Transfer files, 1983 August (Box 33)
      - Transportation, Department of (Box 33)
      - Travel Reports (Box 33)
      - State Rail Plan Update, 1982 (Box 33)
      - Travel Authorization Request (Box 34)
      - Travel Reports, DEP (Box 34)
      - Treasure Chest Inc., Windsor Locks (Box 34)
      - Treasurer, State of Connecticut (Box 34)
      - Tri-Chem (Box 34)
      - U (Miscellaneous) (Box 34)
      - Underground Storage (Box 34)
      - Union Carbide Corp. (Box 34)
      - Uniroyal (Box 34)
      - United Illuminating, 80 Temple St. (Box 34)
      - U.S. Army Resources (Box 34)
      - U.S. Dept of Interior (Box 34)
      - U.S. Marine Corp. (Box 34)
      - USS Nautilus Memorial Development Plan (Box 34)
      - U.S. Naval Submarine Base (Box 34)
      - U.S. Saving Bonds Program (Box 34)
      - United Technologies Corp. (Box 34)
      - United Way/Combined Health Appeal (Box 34)
      - University of Connecticut (UCONN) (Box 34)
      - University of Connecticut (UCONN)-Incinerator (Box 34)
      - Urban Conservation Corps Program (Box 35)
      - Utility Contractors Association (Box 35)
      - V (Miscellaneous) (Box 35)
      - Valley Railroad Company, The Essex (Box 35)
      - Vehicles, DAS (Box 35)
      - CSU DEP Vehicle Assignment List (Box 35)
      - Vermont, State of Agency Environ (Box 35)
      - Vernon, CT (Box 35)
      - Voluntown, Town of (Box 35)
      - W (Miscellaneous) (Box 35)
      - Wadsworth Atheneum (Box 35)
      - Wallingford, Town of (Box 35)
      - Water Compliance, Current and Previous Year (Box 35)
      - Water Conservation (Box 35)
      - Water Diversion (Box 35)
      - Water Pollution Program (Box 35)
      - Water Resources (Box 35)
      - Water Quality (Box 35)
      - Water Resources, the Institute (Box 35)
      - Water Resources (Box 36)
      - Housatonic Scenic River (Box 36)
      - Water Service Consolidation (Box 36)
      - Water Supply System (Box 36)
      - Waterbury State Technical College (Box 36)
      - Waterbury, Town of (Box 36)
      - Weed Harvesting Equipment (Box 36)
      - Westbrook, Town of (Box 36)
      - West Hartford, Town of (Box 36)
      - West Haven, City of (Box 36)
      - West River Flood Control (Box 36)
      - Westport (Box 37)
      - Western District Headquarters (Box 37)
      - Wethersfield (Box 37)
      - Wetlands (Box 37)
      - White Memorial Foundation (Box 37)
      - Whitefield Manor (Box 37)
      - Wild Animal (Box 37)
      - Willington (Box 37)
      - Williams Pond Dam Lake (Box 37)
      - Willow Brook Flooding (Box 37)
      - Wilton (Box 37)
      - Windham (Box 37)
      - Windham Regional Energy Recovery Inc. (Box 37)
      - Windsor (Box 37)
      - Windsor Locks Landfill (Box 37)
      - Acid Rain (Box 2)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 2)
      - Coastal Area Management (Box 2)
      - Coal Conversion (Box 2)
      - CPTV (Box 2)
      - CRRA (Box 2)
      - CT River Assembly (Box 2)
      - Council on Environmental Quality (Box 2)
      - Drinking Water (Box 2)
      - Education (Box 2)
      - Energy (Box 2)
      - Flood Control (Box 2)
    - Subject Files, 1973-1980; 1988-024 (part)
      - Acid Rain, 1980 June-December (Box 13-5)
      - Acid Rain, 1980 January-June (Box 13-5)
      - EPA Reports on Acid Rain, 1980 January (Box 13-5)
      - EPA Reports on Acid Rain, 1977 June (Box 13-5)
      - EPA Booklets, Etc., Pertaining to Air. (Box 13-5)
      - Acid Rain, 1979 (Box 13-5)
      - Adjudication’s-General Information, Etc. (Box 13-5)
      - Adjudication’s Unit DEP Final Decisions, 1980 (Box 13-5)
      - Final Decisions-1981 Adjudication’s (Box 13-5)
      - Administrative (DEP) (Box 13-5)
      - DAS-State Dept. of Administrative Services, 1980 January - 1981 August (Box 13-5)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 13-5)
      - Aging, Department of (Box 13-5)
      - Agriculture (Box 13-5)
      - Air Compliance, 1977 January - 1980 December (Box 13-5)
      - DEP Air Compliance, 1977-1978 (Box 13-5)
      - Air Compliance (Senate Bill 841) (Box 13-5)
      - CT. Air Quality Summary, 1980 (Box 13-5)
      - CT. Air Quality Summary, 1979 (Box 13-5)
      - CT. Air Quality Summary, 1975-1977 (Box 13-5)
      - Algae Control (Box 13-15)
      - Ansonia Incinerator (Box 13-15)
      - Appalachian Trail (Box 13-15)
      - Appalachian Trailways News (Box 13-15)
      - Aquaculture (Box 13-15)
      - Dept. of the Army Corps of Engineers (Box 13-15)
      - Asbestos (Box 13-15)
      - Asbestos, 1977 (Box 13-15)
      - Attorney General, 1980 (Box 13-15)
      - Attorney General, 1979 (Box 13-15)
      - Asbestos Information from Housatonic Comm. College, 1977 March 3 (Box 13-15)
      - Bantam Lake Restoration Project (Box 13-15)
      - Bantam Lake (Box 13-15)
      - Bartholomew’s Lake (Box 13-15)
      - Beacon Falls (Box 13-15)
      - Beaver Dam Lake (Box 13-15)
      - Bi-Project Status (Box 13-15)
      - Bluff Point - Groton (Box 13-15)
      - Bluff Point Environmental Impact Statement (Box 13-15)
      - Boat Ramps (Box 13-15)
      - Boating (Box 13-15)
      - Bond Commission, 1979 (Box 13-15)
      - Bottle Bill Report, 1975 January (Box 13-15)
      - Bottle Bill Report - No Deposit No Return -NY, 1975 February (Box 13-16)
      - Bottle Bill Report to General Assembly, 1975 (Box 13-16)
      - Bottle Bill (no dates), 1975 (Box 13-16)
      - Bottle Bill, 1976-1978 September (Box 13-16)
      - Bottle Bill, 1977 October - 1978 December (Box 13-16)
      - Bottle Bill, 1979 (Box 13-16)
      - Bottle Bill, 1980 (Box 13-16)
      - Branford, Town of (Box 13-16)
      - Bridgeport, Town of (Box 13-16)
      - Bristol, Town of, 1978 November - 1980 December (Box 13-16)
      - Brookfield, 1972 January - 1979 November (Box 13-16)
      - BTU Bubble, 1979 December - 1980 September (Box 13-16)
      - Budget, 1977 January - 1980 April (Box 13-20)
      - Budget Summary of Fiscal Year, 1979 (Box 13-20)
      - DEP Budget Request (Box 13-20)
      - Building, 1976 November - 1980 November (Box 13-20)
      - Canaan Airport Study, 1977 August (Box 13-20)
      - Canaan Airport, 1977 August (Box 13-20)
      - Candlewood Lake, 1975 January - 1980 November (Box 13-20)
      - Carcinogenic, 1977 January - 1980 August (Box 13-20)
      - Citizen’s Advisory Council, 1977 January - 1980 January (Box 13-20)
      - Civil Preparedness, 1977 January - 1980 November (Box 13-20)
      - Clean Air Acts, 1976 January - 1980 December (Box 13-20)
      - Coal Conversion Report- Bridgeport Harbor Station, 1979 December (Box 13-20)
      - Coal Conversion, 1980 January-December (Box 13-20)
      - Coal Conversion, 1974 August-1979 December (Box 13-20)
      - CAM, 1977 May - 1980 December (Box 13-3)
      - CAM Coastal Goals and Policies-Planning Reports #26, 1978 August (Box 13-3)
      - Colchester/Hampton Sewers, 1977 October - 1980 August (Box 13-3)
      - Colchester Landfill, 1977 December - 1978 November (Box 13-3)
      - Colchester Landfill, 1979 March-1980 December (Box 13-3)
      - Combustion Equipment Associates, 1977 (Box 13-3)
      - Combustion Equipment Associates, 1978-1980 (Box 13-3)
      - Commissioner’s Personal, 1977 July-1980 November (Box 13-3)
      - Commodore Marina, 1977 April-1980 June (Box 13-3)
      - Communications (DEP), 1980 March (Box 13-3)
      - Comptroller’s Office State of Connecticut, 1977 January-1978 January (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Academy of Science and Engineering (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Alcohol and Drug Abuse Council FY79 Report (Box 13-3)
      - CT Assoc. of Conservation & Inland Wetlands Commission, 1978 August - November (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Assoc. of Soil & Water Conservation Districts, 1977 March-1980 December (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Conference of Municipalities Newspapers, 1977 January-February (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Construction Industries Assoc., Inc. (Box 13-3)
      - CEPA, 1977 March-1980 October (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Forest & Park Association, 1977 March - 1978 February (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Horse Council, 1978 April - 1979 October (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Industry Museum, 1980 February 11 (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Marine Trades Association, Inc., 1980 June + 1980 December (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Public Transit Authority, 1980 September - 1980 December (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Public Transit Authority, 1980 March - 1980 July (Box 13-3)
      - CT. Public Transit Authority, 1970 December - 1980 February (Box 13-3)
      - CRRA, 1980 October (Box 13-3)
      - CRRA, 1980 August - 1980 December (Box 13-3)
      - CRRA, 1980 June-1980 July (Box 13-10)
      - CRRA, 1980 January - 1980 May (Box 13-10)
      - CRRA, 1977 January-April, 1979 March-December (Box 13-10)
      - CT. River Assembly, 1979 May+1980 February (Box 13-10)
      - CT. River Basin Plan (Report), 1976 June (Box 13-10)
      - CT. River Gateway Commission, 1977 June-1980 October (Box 13-10)
      - CT. River Valley Flood Control Program, 1978 June-1980 October (Box 13-10)
      - CT. River Water Diversion, 1977 October-1980 September (Box 13-10)
      - CT. Science Fair, 1980 February-1980 March (Box 13-10)
      - CT. Soil and Water Conservation Districts- Inventory Report 1978 (Box 13-10)
      - CT. Urban Task Force, 1978 April-1980 October (Box 13-10)
      - Conservation Officers (Box 13-10)
      - Conservation + Preservation, 1977 September-1980 November (Box 13-10)
      - Construction Grants, 1977 March-1980 November (Box 13-10)
      - Consulting Engineers, 1977 February 2+7 (Box 13-10)
      - Council on Environmental Quality, 1977 June-1980 October (Box 13-10)
      - Council on Environmental Quality (Box 13-10)
      - Eastern Region Conference of the Council of State Governments (Box 13-10)
      - Crystal Mall, Waterford, 1979 December - 1980 October (Box 13-10)
      - Dams, 1977 February-1980 December (Box 13-10)
      - Data Processing, 1973 September-1980 June (Box 13-10)
      - Debriefing Memos (Box 13-10)
      - Delegation Letters, 1980 April-1980 September (Box 13-10)
      - DEP Directives, 1977 September-1980 August (Box 13-10)
      - Dredging Disposal of Dangerous Materials in Long Island Sound (Box 13-10)
      - Dredging, 1977 February-1980 October (Box 13-10)
      - Dredging - Long Island Sound (New Haven/ Stamford), 1977 July - 1980 February (Box 13-10)
      - Dredging - Bio. Study, 1977 July (Box 13-10)
      - Drinking Water, Water Compliance Unit, 1977 June-1980 September (Box 13-7)
      - Emergency Operations Plan St. of CT., 1976 (Box 13-7)
      - Energy (Box 13-7)
      - Energy Advisory Board, 1977 January-1980 December (Box 13-7)
      - Energy, 1980 April-1980 November (Box 13-7)
      - Energy, 1974 August-1980 March (Box 13-7)
      - EPA (Box 13-7)
      - Environmental Achievements (Box 13-7)
      - Fairfield, Town of (Box 13-7)
      - Environmental Quality, 1975 May-1980 December (Box 13-7)
      - Federal Paperboard, 1979 March-1980 November (Box 13-7)
      - Federal Water Pollution Control Act, 1977 February-1980 June (Box 13-7)
      - DEP Fisheries Unit, 1977 June-1980 December (Box 13-7)
      - Fish and Water life, 1977 March-1980 June (Box 13-7)
      - Fish life - ASMFC Reports (4ea), 1976, 1977-1979 September (Box 13-7)
      - Flood Control, 1977 March-1980 October (Box 13-8)
      - Fluorocarbons, 1977 January-1977 August (Box 13-8)
      - Forestry, 1978 July-1980 February (Box 13-8)
      - Forestry, 1980 March-1980 November (Box 13-8)
      - Forestry- Fuel wood, 1978 December-1980 September (Box 13-8)
      - Fort Griswold, 1980 June-1980 September (Box 13-8)
      - Gasoline Allocations, 1977 June-1980 October (Box 13-8)
      - General Assembly Legislative Program Review, 1979 February (Box 13-8)
      - Gillette Castle (Box 13-8)
      - Glasco Dam (Box 13-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1980 October-1980 December (Box 13-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1980 August-1980 September (Box 13-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1980 January-1980 July (Box 13-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1977 April-1980 July (Box 13-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1978 December-1980 June (Box 13-8)
      - Groton Sewer Outfall, 1976 October-1980 June (Box 13-8)
      - Groundwater Contamination, 1980 February-1980 December (Box 13-8)
      - Gypsy Moths, 1980 August-1980 December (Box 13-8)
      - Hamden, Town of (Box 13-8)
      - Hammonassett State Park, 1977 February-1980 December (Box 13-8)
      - Hancock Brook Shooting Range (Box 13-8)
      - Handicapped Recreation, 1977 August-1980 June (Box 13-8)
      - Harkness Memorial State Park, 1977 march-1980 September (Box 13-8)
      - Hazardous Materials Management Unit, 1980 January-1980 May (Box 13-8)
      - Hazardous Materials Management, 1979 October-1979 December (Box 13-8)